<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
  <plugin id="com.jonnyzzz.mcp-steroid" url="https://github.com/jonnyzzz/mcp-steroid/releases/download/0.89.0/mcp-steroid-0.89.0.zip" version="0.89.0">
    <idea-version since-build="253"/>
    <name>MCP Steroid</name>
    <vendor>jonnyzzz.com</vendor>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><b>MCP Steroid</b> brings the full power of the IntelliJ Platform to AI agents through the Model Context Protocol (MCP).</p>
<p>IntelliJ platform works for AI agents as great as for human developers.</p>
<ul>
<li><b>9 MCP Tools:</b> Control IntelliJ IDEA programmatically — execute code, take screenshots, discover actions, debug, and more</li>
<li><b>58 MCP Resources:</b> Comprehensive guides covering LSP, IDE operations, debugger, tests, VCS, and more</li>
<li><b>Vision Capabilities:</b> AI agents can see your IDE with screenshots and OCR</li>
<li><b>Deep Integration:</b> Access PSI, inspections, refactorings, and full IntelliJ Platform API</li>
<li><b>Human Oversight:</b> Review and approve code execution with configurable safety controls</li>
</ul>
<p>Compatible with all IntelliJ Platform-based IDEs: IntelliJ IDEA, PyCharm, WebStorm, GoLand, CLion, Rider, and more.</p>
<p>Requirements: IntelliJ IDEA 2025.3 or newer (build 253 or later).</p>
<p>Visit <a href="https://mcp-steroid.jonnyzzz.com">mcp-steroid.jonnyzzz.com</a> for documentation and examples.</p>]]></description>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[<h2>What's New in v0.89.0</h2>
<h3>Demo: Codex Debugs in IntelliJ IDEA</h3>
<p>[![Codex debugs an application in IntelliJ IDEA](https://img.youtube.com/vi/HtDDNyAoLak/hqdefault.jpg)](https://youtu.be/HtDDNyAoLak)</p>
<p>In this video, Codex debugs an application in IntelliJ IDEA. The demo is powered by the MCP Steroid plugin for IntelliJ-based IDEs, https://mcp-steroid.jonnyzzz.com.</p>
<h3>Codex Agent Output Support</h3>
<p>Full support for Codex NDJSON output format — handles `mcp_tool_call` items with their distinct field names (`tool` instead of `name`, `arguments` instead of `input`), structured result objects, and `reasoning` items rendered as `[thinking]` blocks. Raw and decoded agent logs are now saved per prompt run.</p>
<h3>Prompt System Overhaul</h3>
<li>Migrated all articles from multi-file (header + kts) to single-file `.md` format</li>
<li>Merged `-see-also.md` files into main article files</li>
<li>Added `###_NO_AUTO_TOC_###` / `###_EXCLUDE_FROM_AUTO_TOC_###` directives for fine-grained TOC control</li>
<li>Per-article read tests are now auto-generated</li>
<li>Removed old-format article support from buildSrc codegen</li>
<li>Migrated tool descriptions to prompt article resources</li>
<h3>Docker Test Infrastructure Refactoring</h3>
<p>Major refactoring of the Docker container process runner and agent infrastructure:</p>
<li>Replaced `runInContainer` with `startProcessInContainer` across all drivers</li>
<li>Consolidated container process types into `docker-container-exec-detached.kt`</li>
<li>Channel-driven stdin for `ConsoleDriver` (replacing per-line docker exec)</li>
<li>Real-time console pumping in `ConsoleAwareAgentSession` with raw + decoded log files</li>
<li>Interactive docker exec support (`-i` flag)</li>
<li>Coroutines `Channel` for `ProcessRunner` output (no busy loop)</li>
<h3>DPAIA Arena Testing</h3>
<p>Introduced Docker-based A/B comparison testing infrastructure (DPAIA — Developer Productivity AI Assessment) for measuring agent effectiveness with vs without MCP Steroid. Includes automated test pipeline with iterative improvement loops, bare git repo caching, JDK auto-configuration, Maven/Gradle import awaiting, and per-product smoke tests.</p>
<h3>Plugin & Build Improvements</h3>
<li>Extracted plugin build into dedicated `ij-plugin/` subproject</li>
<li>Plugin deployment hot-reload via `deployPlugin` task</li>
<li>MCP server now starts at IDE startup via `AppLifecycleListener`</li>
<li>`execution_id` made optional in `steroid_execute_feedback`</li>
<li>Release builds only include release notes in `plugin.xml` (skip for snapshots)</li>
<li>Upload LICENSE to GitHub releases with full URLs</li>
<h3>Settings & UI</h3>
<li>New MCP Steroid project settings page (Tools > MCP Steroid) with copy buttons and structured connection info</li>
<li>Human review workflow reworked: renamed actions, `isReviewRequired()` logic, Always Allow option with warning icon</li>
<li>Screenshot capture now includes modal dialogs</li>
<h3>Agent Compatibility</h3>
<li>Claude Code 2.1.x new structured event format support in `ClaudeOutputFilter` (handles both old streaming and new structured formats)</li>
<li>Output filters pass through unknown JSON events (future-proof)</li>
<li>Generic `toolDetail()` extracts human-readable summary for all known tools</li>
<h3>Stability & Bug Fixes</h3>
<li>Fixed AIPromoWindowAdvisor 8-minute startup deadlock in Docker containers</li>
<li>Fixed Islands Theme onboarding dialog blocking test containers</li>
<li>Fixed `CodeButcher` import extraction from triple-quoted string literals</li>
<li>Fixed AiAgentDriver NPE with lazy property ordering</li>
<li>Fixed DISPLAY env var propagation in container processes</li>
<li>Fixed Docker reaper image tagging and container ancestry filter</li>
<li>Renamed "IntelliJ MCP Steroid" to "MCP Steroid" across codebase</li>
<h3>Build & Infrastructure</h3>
<li>KtBlocks compilation test infrastructure for verifying code examples in prompt articles</li>
<li>`ScriptClassLoaderFactory` interface for test classpath isolation</li>
<li>Compilation tests made stable across build re-runs</li>
<li>Increased IDE window detection timeout with better diagnostics</li>
<li>Concurrent test run protection documented (shared `idea-sandbox/` corruption)</li>
<p>Full release notes: <a href="https://mcp-steroid.jonnyzzz.com/releases/0.89.0/">mcp-steroid.jonnyzzz.com/releases/0.89.0/</a></p>]]></change-notes>
  </plugin>
</plugins>

